[{"answer": "At the airport. Tomorrow. When they provide the plane to fly him and the hostages to that place. my friend evidently feels very comfortable in that place", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "They've got no choice, my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You spoke English well enough to your contact... the street vendor... so please let's not play games. We're both professionals, my friend", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yes, I know what your name is... my friend..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yes, I know what your name is... my friend..", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Alias my friend, alias my friend, alias The Jackal", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh yeah... I didn't recognize you without my foot chained to the floor", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "There are a lot of hard feelings. And I'm still gonna sue you when this is over", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah..", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I want you to come now..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Your business", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Pipes", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "For the oil..", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Pipes for oil... Petroleum..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " I not order nothing", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Iced water", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Why not?! That way they wouldn't have tried to kill me and I wouldn't have wound up killing them", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Too dangerous... what the fuck do you think that was back there? Safe? How the fuck more dangerous does it have to get", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Get out of here... now..", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Get out now..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I don't want anybody workin' on the car. Car needs something I'll do it. But I don't want anybody touchin' that car", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It makes a difference to me okay? So don't do it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah well I don't have much to say about it. It's the that place you know", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What's hurting us", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You can request another assignment. It's changed you that place. It's hurting us", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Your attitude... that's what hurting us", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Me... My ass is on the line too", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "If the Russians don't go for the bait for any reason you will have gotten out of there at twent", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Who cares? This isn't you and me. It's me and him. If the Russians don't go for the bait for any reason..", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "If the Russians don't go for the bait for any reason, I'll go in there and kill him myself. And if I'm still alive I might just come looking for you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Hi... listen, do you and that place want to come over with the kids for a barbeque this afternoon", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Okay, call me when you get back", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I'm so sorry", "docId": "Assignment_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No one is better off dead I think", "qsentId": 34}]